<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Learning on Satish Eshwar</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Learning on Satish Eshwar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.140.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What keeps me awake other than work😉</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interests/interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interests/interests/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;badprobabilitycom&#34;&gt;BadProbability.com&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love this name, and I might put a lot of my creative works into this domain. But the domain itself is where I explore the unpredictable nature of life and decision-making. The concept centers around the role of probability in our everyday choices, actions, and beliefs, highlighting both favorable and unfavorable outcomes. The name &lt;a href=&#34;http://BadProbability.com&#34;&gt;BadProbability.com&lt;/a&gt; was chosen intentionally to focus on the often-overlooked, less glamorous side of probability—the &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; outcomes that shape our experiences and how life&amp;rsquo;s uncertainties and setbacks play a significant role in our personal growth and adaptation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking into Cybersecurity: My Journey of Learning and Resilience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/20241225_breaking_into_cybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/20241225_breaking_into_cybersecurity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;tagline&#34;&gt;Tagline&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You can only connect the dots in hindsight Take every opportunity to learn, even if you don’t know what’s best at the time… Give it your best shot, absorb the learnings, and move forward.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With over &lt;strong&gt;20 years in IT&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;15+ years specializing in security&lt;/strong&gt;, I currently serve as an advisor at a US MNC. My expertise spans various domains, including Identity, Vulnerability Management, Incident Response, Audit, Controls, Compliance, Third-Party Security, and Application Security.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
